Wow! We are here in Okinawa!
I was worried about rain, but the first day is sunny.
They say it's fresh. I'm so excited! It's so hot!
I'll do my best!
Here we are at the beach. It's still sunny.
It's so nice!
Watch out! I almost hit a leaf.
So beautiful! Please take a look.
It's so beautiful! Please look at it.
It's like "Bon appétit!
Looks delicious!
How do you hold it?
Bon appétit!
Sounds fun.
Okay, let's go.
I'm not much of an ocean person.
But I love the ocean in Okinawa.
Beautiful
Oh, it's going to be fun! Looks like fun! Looks like fun!
Oh, fun!
Oh, nice street!
I like it! That's good!
Day 1 of the shoot is over!
It was a lot of fun!
We managed to beat the Okinawan weather on the first day.
The scenery was beautiful and the sunset is just now.
I'm looking forward to the second day tomorrow, when we will go to the aquarium!
I will do my best on the second day!
Good morning.
It started suddenly.
It's the Chula Sea Aquarium, a footnote.
I feel amazingly happy.
I miss coming here with all the worshippers a long time ago.
Surprisingly, the picture might be pretty clear.
I think it's a happy aquarium.
Menderenai-.
It started suddenly.
Surprisingly, I think I may have captured it quite clearly.
I think it's a happy aquarium.
I miss the time when I came here with all of Worcester a long time ago.
I think I might have taken a surprisingly clear picture.
It's nice.
Cute.
There's someone watching, because...
Oh, there they are! Are you there? Are you there?
Oh, my God!
Oh, he's so cute! She's so cute!
He's so energetic!
He's so cute!
That's awesome!
Oh, I see it!
Good, good, good, good, good.
Good, good, good.
It's so cute.
It's great.
Oh, no.
Already disassembled
No, no, no.
Thank you very much.
How did it feel?
I don't know.
Slippery, slippery, slippery.
Let's get next to it.
Slippery.
Good, good, good, good, good, good, good.
Oh, my God.
Oh, wow.
Wow.
That's great.
Se-no.
Ooh.
Great, great, great, great, great.
Wow.
That's great.
Here it comes.
It's like this.
Wow, that's great.
That's great.
Thank you so much.
Wow.
That's awesome.
Cute.
Amazing.
That's great.
Okay, that's good. That's good.
When it's this good.
Oh, good.
They're traveling.
Adults are crazy about sea turtles.
Amazing Okinawan sea.
Okay, that's it.
Bye bye.
That's the end of the line.
Belly is leaving now
I don't know if I'm going to get a boat or not.
I'm looking forward to it because it's a crushed ship
I wonder how long it will take him to get out.
I hope it doesn't rain.
Here we go.
It's pretty high.
Aren't you afraid?
I'm on my cell phone.
Hey, drop it, you idiot!
Hessi.
[ED]
I'm hungry, I'm hungry, I'm hungry, I'm hungry, I'm hungry, I'm hungry, I'm hungry, I'm hungry, I'm eating, eating.
Eating while eating, eating while eating, not caring about anything.
It tastes so good!
Tastes so good!
Tastes good?
Dashi?
Dashi is delicious.
I came home.
Lunch was so good.
Okay, OK.
I'm squatting, so and so, so and so.
Okay, go, go, go.
Okay, OK.
Good night.
Okay, here we go.
Okay, this is good. This is good.
Did we just do the same pose for a second?
Island pose.
Oh, it's playing, it's playing.
Oh, yeah, that's good. Oh, yeah, that's great.
Is it coming out?
All right.
Finally, I've been wanting to come here for a long time, and now I've got to go.
I'm so happy. It's a strange place to be.
It's a strange feeling.
Oh, you're playing. You're playing.
No, really.
Thank you very much.
Good job.
That's great.
I'm so happy.
Good job, guys.
That's great.
Thank you very much.
Second day is over.Day 2 is over.
It was fun.
Tomorrow is the last day.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for your hard work.
3rd day of photo book shooting
It's the last day
It was fine.
I don't know what the weather will be like after this.
quickly.
I'll do my best to make it quick.
I'll enjoy it.
The sound of rain is faint and blurred.
I'm chasing after it, but it won't catch up with me. I like that kind of feeling.
Between the bells of a dream, words are not enough to show it
The scenery that comes to mind...
The voice of the cameraman is filming
Go beyond the third dimension
It's so sunny.
What is this place again? The harbor... no.
A row of nails.
What?
Nail trees.
rows of nails
nails
nail?
nail
rows of nails
Fukugi-san
Fukugi-san, you're not listening at all!
We came to "Fukugi Namiki" (rows of trees lined with nails)
It's so clear!
It looks more beautiful than before
Cute red dog-keeshon!
Amazing!
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
It's coming so fast!
The wind is too strong!
But it's so clear.
If it were true, I wouldn't be in there.
That's a good blue.
This is not good.
Oh, it's fine.
The sun is shining, the best weather we've had in Okinawa. They say it's too cold but it might get better.
The red dress looks amazing.
Cute.
Also, I'll do my best for the rest of the shoot!
Can you notice my love?
Here we are at Kokusai-dori.
It's already getting late in the evening.
I hope to be able to shop on Kokusai-dori!
I'm looking forward to it!
He said it's absolutely delicious.
It's absolutely delicious!
Yes, it is!
I got 1,000 yen and bought 240 yen.
Wow, it's good, it's good, it's good.
Here we are at the last place!
What a crazy beautiful place!
Winners!
This place could be fun, like nature.
It sure is.
Wow, this place is amazing!
Staff ан applause!
Oh!
We also talked to some beginners.
How did you like it? First time photographing beginners
We were lucky.
In the freedom of Okinawa.
It was a little difficult to get close.
I'm glad you came close.
I wanted to come when I saw the page too
I'm glad you did.
I wasn't even a little bit nervous about the day.
Today was amazing
while I was yuriing.
Thank you for watching this song!
I'll do my best!
I hope you all do well, my assistants!
Good results in the middle of the day!
See you again!
It was fun!
Mr. Fukuki didn't understand me at all.
Namiki Fukuki